<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The place for kids to learn Martial Arts and Self Defense on Rei Martial Arts</title>
    <link>https://reima.com.au/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The place for kids to learn Martial Arts and Self Defense on Rei Martial Arts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://reima.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://reima.com.au/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reima.com.au/contact/</guid>
      <description>You are welcome to call us on 0432 785 795 or just submit a form below: Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids classes</title>
      <link>https://reima.com.au/kids-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reima.com.au/kids-classes/</guid>
      <description>When? Here is our timetable:
 Tuesday: 6.30pm - 7.30pm
 Friday: 6.30pm - 7.30pm  What about prices?  Here they are:
 Joining fee - $0
 Annual fee - $0
 1 months of classes - $100  
Bonuses  1) We offer 2 week free trial!
2) For each additional month you pay in advance you get $20 off!
 For example: if you decide to pay 3 months in advance you will get (3months x $20) $60 off which will bring your payment down to $240 instead of $300!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://reima.com.au/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reima.com.au/location/</guid>
      <description>Our classes are held at Beecroft Uniting Church - 82 Beecroft road, Beecroft.
The location is just 5 minutes walking from Beecroft train station or 2 minutes from Beecroft Place.
Here is the map:  If you have any question, don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to call us on 0432 785 795.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Martial Arts for kids</title>
      <link>https://reima.com.au/articles/what-is-martial-arts-for-kids/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://reima.com.au/articles/what-is-martial-arts-for-kids/</guid>
      <description>Martial arts isn&amp;rsquo;t all about kicking and punching. Violent TV shows and movies might be responsible for some of the bad rap that the sport gets; in reality, martial arts will help your child much more than it will hurt.
Whether your kid is bursting with energy or shy in most social situations, martial arts can go a long way toward developing qualities and habits in your young ones that can last a lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>